The	O
1	BUILD
Barracks	OBUILD
Fast	OBUILD
Expand	OBUILD
is	O
a	O
build	O
which	O
aims	O
to	O
create	O
an	O
economic	O
advantage	O
for	O
the	O
Terran	PERSON
,	O
without	O
being	O
as	O
risky	O
as	O
14	BUILD
CC	BUILD
.	O
It	O
negates	O
much	O
of	O
the	O
effectiveness	O
of	O
the	O
12	BUILD
Nexus	BUILD
build	O
.	O
The	O
build	O
can	O
also	O
be	O
done	O
in	O
response	O
to	O
a	O
Protoss	RACE
gas	O
steal	O
.	O
9	SUPPLY
-	O
Depot	BUILDING
11	SUPPLY
-	O
Barracks	BUILDING
15	SUPPLY
-	O
Command	BUILDING
Center	BUILDING
16	SUPPLY
-	O
Depot	BUILDING
16	SUPPLY
-	O
Refinery	BUILDING
16	SUPPLY
-	O
2	NUMBER
Marines	UNIT
-LSB-	O
1	NUMBER
-RSB-	O
16	SUPPLY
-	O
Depot	BUILDING
-LSB-	O
2	NUMBER
-RSB-	O
17	SUPPLY
-	O
Command	BUILDING
Center	BUILDING
18	SUPPLY
-	O
Refinery	BUILDING
21	SUPPLY
-	O
Factory	BUILDING
-LSB-	O
3	NUMBER
-RSB-	O
21	SUPPLY
-	O
Bunker	BUILDING
@	LOCATION
Natural	LOCATION
Expansion	LOCATION
-LSB-	O
4	NUMBER
-RSB-	O
-LSB-	O
5	NUMBER
-RSB-	O
-LSB-	O
6	NUMBER
-RSB-	O
25	SUPPLY
-	O
Factory	BUILDING
-LSB-	O
3	NUMBER
-RSB-	O
28	SUPPLY
-	O
Depot	BUILDING
30	SUPPLY
-	O
Refinery	BUILDING
@	LOCATION
Natural	LOCATION
Expansion	LOCATION
-LSB-	O
7	NUMBER
-RSB-	O
31	SUPPLY
-	O
Siege	UNIT
Tank	UNIT
and	O
Siege	UPGRADE
Mode	UPGRADE
37	SUPPLY
-	O
Depot	BUILDING
44	SUPPLY
-	O
Engineering	BUILDING
Bay	BUILDING
25	SUPPLY
-	O
Engineering	BUILDING
Bay	BUILDING
-LSB-	O
8	NUMBER
-RSB-	O
28	SUPPLY
-	O
Siege	UNIT
Tank	UNIT
and	O
Siege	UPGRADE
Mode	UPGRADE
↑	O
Marines	UNIT
can	O
be	O
skipped	O
if	O
the	O
Protoss	PERSON
does	O
n't	O
open	O
with	O
an	O
aggressive	O
Build	O
Order	O
↑	O
Marine	UNIT
production	O
depends	O
on	O
the	O
scouting	O
timing	O
.	O
If	O
Protoss	PERSON
did	O
not	O
scout	O
yet	O
,	O
Marine	UNIT
production	O
can	O
be	O
delayed	O
until	O
after	O
the	O
Command	BUILDING
Center	BUILDING
was	O
started	O
↑	O
3.0	NUMBER
3.1	NUMBER
Machine	BUILDING
Shop	BUILDING
is	O
added	O
when	O
the	O
Factory	BUILDING
finishes	O
↑	O
The	O
Bunker	BUILDING
may	O
be	O
built	O
at	O
18	SUPPLY
Supply	O
if	O
Protoss	PERSON
opens	O
with	O
an	O
aggressive	O
opening	O
↑	NUMBER
The	O
Bunker	BUILDING
can	O
be	O
skipped	O
if	O
the	O
Protoss	PERSON
does	O
n't	O
open	O
with	O
an	O
aggressive	O
Build	O
Order	O
↑	NUMBER
The	O
Bunker	BUILDING
placement	O
is	O
important	O
.	O
See	O
also	O
:	O
Execution	O
↑	NUMBER
Timing	O
:	O
second	ORDINAL
Machine	BUILDING
Shop	BUILDING
and	O
Geyser	BUILDING
should	O
be	O
built	O
around	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
↑	NUMBER
@	PERCENT
100	PERCENT
%	PERCENT
Engineering	BUILDING
Bay	BUILDING
:	O
Secure	O
base	O
with	O
Turrets	BUILDING
The	DURATION
first	DURATION
few	DURATION
minutes	DURATION
of	O
the	O
opening	O
are	O
straight	O
forward	O
and	O
do	O
not	O
need	O
any	O
further	O
explanation	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
noted	O
that	O
efficient	O
scouting	O
is	O
pivotal	O
for	O
the	O
Build	O
Order	O
.	O
The	O
reaction	O
of	O
Protoss	PERSON
dictates	O
the	O
further	O
path	O
of	O
the	O
Terran	PERSON
Build	O
Order	O
described	O
previously	DATE
.	O
If	O
Protoss	PERSON
chooses	O
to	O
play	O
aggressive	O
early	O
on	O
,	O
Terran	PERSON
needs	O
to	O
build	O
two	NUMBER
Marines	UNIT
at	O
16	SUPPLY
Supply	O
and	O
the	O
Bunker	BUILDING
already	O
at	O
18	SUPPLY
Supply	O
.	O
Early	O
pressure	O
can	O
mean	O
anything	O
from	O
a	O
two	BUILD
Gateway	BUILD
Proxy	BUILD
Zealot	BUILD
rush	BUILD
,	O
which	O
generally	O
hard	O
counters	O
this	O
opening	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
10/15	SUPPLY
Gateway	BUILDING
strategy	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
latter	O
,	O
strong	O
Dragoon	UNIT
pressure	O
,	O
the	O
placement	O
of	O
the	O
Bunker	BUILDING
plays	O
an	O
important	O
role	O
.	O
It	O
should	O
be	O
built	O
in	O
a	O
way	O
,	O
that	O
Dragoons	UNIT
can	O
not	O
attack	O
the	O
mineral	O
patches	O
of	O
the	LOCATION
Natural	LOCATION
Expansion	LOCATION
,	O
nor	O
should	O
a	O
greater	O
mass	O
of	O
Dragoons	UNIT
be	O
able	O
to	O
simply	O
run	O
past	DATE
the	O
Bunker	BUILDING
.	O
Once	DATE
the	O
Bunker	BUILDING
is	O
under	O
attack	O
,	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
repaired	O
instantly	O
.	O
A	O
rule	O
of	O
thumb	O
suggests	O
that	O
one	NUMBER
SCV	UNIT
per	O
Dragoon	UNIT
should	O
be	O
used	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
also	O
important	O
to	O
regularly	O
check	O
the	O
repairing	O
workers	UNIT
,	O
as	O
the	O
process	O
of	O
repairing	O
will	O
automatically	O
be	O
cancelled	O
if	O
the	O
Bunker	BUILDING
was	O
restored	O
to	O
full	O
health	O
.	O
If	O
Protoss	PERSON
is	O
scouted	O
late	O
and	O
therefore	O
scouting	O
information	O
misses	O
,	O
Terran	PERSON
can	O
chose	O
to	O
alter	O
the	O
Build	O
Order	O
for	O
the	O
opening	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
described	O
in	O
the	O
right	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Build	O
Order	O
Table	O
on	O
top	O
of	O
this	O
chapter	O
.	O
An	O
earlier	O
Engineering	BUILDING
Bay	BUILDING
enables	O
the	O
Terran	PERSON
to	O
build	O
Turrets	BUILDING
soon	O
.	O
One	NUMBER
Turret	BUILDING
should	O
be	O
placed	O
immediately	O
after	O
finishing	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
Choke	O
Point	O
to	O
detect	O
incoming	O
Dark	UNIT
Templars	UNIT
,	O
another	O
two	NUMBER
should	O
shield	O
the	O
Main	LOCATION
Base	LOCATION
from	O
incoming	O
Reaver	UNIT
harassment	O
and/or	O
Elevator	UNIT
Shuttles	UNIT
.	O
However	O
,	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
noted	O
that	O
the	O
safe	O
variation	O
also	O
delays	O
any	O
future	DATE
mid	O
game	O
transition	O
significantly	O
.	O
In	O
modern	O
Terran	RACE
vs.	O
Protoss	RACE
,	O
the	O
Protoss	PERSON
will	O
usually	O
try	O
to	O
put	O
pressure	O
early	O
on	O
against	O
the	O
Terran	PERSON
expansion	LOCATION
,	O
before	O
any	O
Siege	UNIT
Tanks	UNIT
are	O
out	O
,	O
while	O
expanding	O
twice	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
.	O
Therefore	O
,	O
most	O
Terran	RACE
players	O
try	O
to	O
transition	O
into	O
the	O
mid-game	O
and	O
prepare	O
for	O
a	O
timed	O
attack	O
,	O
which	O
punishes	O
too	O
greedy	O
expansion	O
behaviour	O
.	O
How	O
this	O
is	O
done	O
and	O
when	O
an	O
attack	O
strikes	O
depends	O
on	O
the	O
Terran	RACE
player	O
.	O
It	O
should	O
be	O
noted	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
opening	O
indeed	O
is	O
more	O
an	O
opening	O
,	O
than	O
an	O
overall	O
game	O
plan	O
.	O
Its	O
ulterior	O
motive	O
is	O
to	O
obtain	O
a	O
good	O
economical	O
basis	O
for	O
the	O
early	O
to	O
mid-game	O
transition	O
.	O
Any	O
kind	O
of	O
Proxy	BUILD
Gateway	BUILD
Rushes	BUILD
usually	O
hard	O
counter	O
this	O
Build	O
Order	O
directly	O
.	O
Only	O
in	O
very	O
few	O
scenarios	O
a	O
Terran	PERSON
can	O
still	O
expand	O
off	O
one	NUMBER
Barracks	BUILDING
against	O
Zealot	UNIT
harassments	O
.	O
Fast	O
and	O
mostly	O
unscouted	O
Tech	MISC
Rushes	MISC
-	O
Dark	UNIT
Templars	UNIT
and	O
Reaver	UNIT
Drops/Elevators	UNIT
-	O
can	O
hard	O
counter	O
the	O
Build	O
Order	O
as	O
well	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
if	O
scouted	O
early	O
on	O
,	O
the	O
Build	O
Order	O
still	O
allows	O
to	O
defend	O
this	O
kind	O
of	O
attack	O
.	O
A	O
12	BUILD
Nexus	BUILD
and	O
2	BUILD
Gateway	BUILD
Dragoon	BUILD
Observer	BUILD
Build	O
Orders	O
are	O
mostly	O
inefficient	O
against	O
a	O
One	BUILD
Barrack	BUILD
Expand	BUILD
.	O
They	O
will	O
leave	O
Protoss	PERSON
with	O
a	O
slight	O
disadvantage	O
in	O
the	O
mid	O
game	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Protoss	PERSON
economy	O
will	O
be	O
slightly	O
weaker	O
than	O
the	O
Terran	PERSON
's	O
.	O
This	O
Build	O
Order	O
can	O
be	O
used	O
on	O
nearly	O
any	O
map	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
wide	O
chokes	O
leading	O
from	O
Natural	LOCATION
Expansion	LOCATION
into	O
the	O
central	O
area	O
of	O
a	O
map	O
put	O
Terran	PERSON
in	O
a	O
slight	O
disadvantage	O
.	O
For	O
instance	O
the	O
wide	O
entrances	O
on	O
Python	MAP
enable	O
the	O
Protoss	PERSON
to	O
apply	O
stronger	O
harassment	O
with	O
Dragoons	UNIT
compared	O
to	O
maps	O
like	O
Destination	MAP
.	O
