The	O
1	NUMBER
Rax	ORGANIZATION
FE	ORGANIZATION
,	O
1	NUMBER
Rax	ORGANIZATION
CC	ORGANIZATION
,	O
or	O
1	NUMBER
Barracks	O
Fast	O
Expansion	O
build	O
is	O
widely	O
considered	O
the	O
standard	O
Terran	MISC
versus	O
Zerg	PERSON
opening	O
for	O
the	O
majority	O
of	O
modern	O
maps	O
.	O
Though	O
the	O
most	O
conventional	O
build	O
aims	O
to	O
counter	O
a	O
Zerg	PERSON
that	O
follows	O
the	O
common	O
3	NUMBER
Hatchery	O
Tech	O
into	O
fast	O
Hive	O
build	O
,	O
the	O
1	NUMBER
Rax	ORGANIZATION
FE	O
build	O
is	O
extremely	O
flexible	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
can	O
be	O
altered	O
to	O
combat	O
almost	O
any	O
build	O
including	O
2	NUMBER
Hatchery	ORGANIZATION
Tech	ORGANIZATION
or	O
a	O
Lair	MISC
Tech	MISC
build	O
,	O
making	O
it	O
a	O
solid	O
build	O
in	O
any	O
situation	O
.	O
The	O
most	O
important	O
thing	O
to	O
know	O
before	O
learning	O
any	O
build	O
,	O
especially	O
the	O
1	NUMBER
Rax	ORGANIZATION
FE	O
build	O
,	O
is	O
the	O
purpose	O
of	O
the	O
build	O
.	O
1	NUMBER
Rax	ORGANIZATION
FE	O
is	O
a	O
starting	O
point	O
and	O
it	O
has	O
many	O
different	O
branches	O
depending	O
on	O
the	O
your	O
plan	O
and	O
the	O
opponent	O
's	O
build	O
.	O
9/10	NUMBER
Supply	O
Depot	O
11/18	NUMBER
-	O
Barracks	O
&	O
scout	O
15-18	NUMBER
Command	O
Center	O
-LRB-	O
See	O
note	O
-RRB-	O
If	O
you	O
scout	O
your	O
opponent	O
in	O
the	O
first	ORDINAL
spot	O
and	O
he	O
is	O
going	O
Hatchery	O
first	ORDINAL
,	O
make	O
the	O
CC	O
at	O
15	NUMBER
and	O
do	O
not	O
make	O
a	O
marine	O
until	O
after	O
depot	O
,	O
unless	O
he	O
scouts	O
you	O
with	O
a	O
Drone	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
see	O
12	NUMBER
Hatch	PERSON
immediately	O
cancel	O
any	O
marines	O
and	O
put	O
up	O
the	O
command	O
center	O
at	O
the	O
natural	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
scout	O
9	NUMBER
pool	O
pull	O
2-3	NUMBER
scvs	O
to	O
your	O
ramp	O
before	O
the	O
lings	O
arrive	O
and	O
make	O
the	O
command	O
center	O
in	O
your	O
main	O
when	O
you	O
have	O
money	O
while	O
keeping	O
constant	O
marine	O
and	O
SCV	O
production	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
build	O
the	O
2nd	ORDINAL
Depot	O
before	O
the	O
Command	ORGANIZATION
Center	ORGANIZATION
you	O
will	O
need	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
third	ORDINAL
Depot	O
before	O
the	O
Command	ORGANIZATION
Center	ORGANIZATION
finishes	O
in	O
order	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
supply	O
blocked	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
made	O
the	O
Command	ORGANIZATION
Center	ORGANIZATION
on	O
15	NUMBER
,	O
it	O
will	O
finish	O
in	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
can	O
build	O
the	O
third	ORDINAL
depot	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Keep	O
your	O
scv	O
near	O
their	O
main	O
hatchery	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
many	O
lings	O
they	O
made	O
when	O
the	O
pool	O
finishes	O
.	O
If	O
they	O
make	O
4-6	NUMBER
lings	O
and	O
leave	O
their	O
base	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
need	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
bunker	O
in	O
case	O
you	O
expanded	O
at	O
the	O
natural	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
lings	O
just	O
chase	O
after	O
your	O
SCV	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
need	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
Zerg	PERSON
does	O
not	O
make	O
their	O
Lair	MISC
within	O
half	O
a	DURATION
minute	DURATION
after	O
their	O
Extractor	MISC
finishes	O
throw	O
down	O
a	O
bunker	O
,	O
supply	O
depot	O
to	O
block	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
SCVs	O
ready	O
to	O
repair	O
and	O
block	O
enemy	O
Zerglings	O
because	O
they	O
researched	O
Zergling	O
Speed	O
first	ORDINAL
and	O
are	O
trying	O
to	O
all-in	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
see	O
12	NUMBER
Hatch	PERSON
immediately	O
cancel	O
any	O
marines	O
and	O
put	O
up	O
the	O
command	O
center	O
at	O
the	O
natural	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
scout	O
9	NUMBER
pool	O
pull	O
2-3	NUMBER
scvs	O
to	O
your	O
ramp	O
before	O
the	O
lings	O
arrive	O
and	O
make	O
the	O
command	O
center	O
in	O
your	O
main	O
when	O
you	O
have	O
money	O
while	O
keeping	O
constant	O
marine	O
and	O
SCV	O
production	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
build	O
the	O
2nd	ORDINAL
Depot	O
before	O
the	O
Command	ORGANIZATION
Center	ORGANIZATION
you	O
will	O
need	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
third	ORDINAL
Depot	O
before	O
the	O
Command	ORGANIZATION
Center	ORGANIZATION
finishes	O
in	O
order	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
supply	O
blocked	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
made	O
the	O
Command	ORGANIZATION
Center	ORGANIZATION
on	O
15	NUMBER
,	O
it	O
will	O
finish	O
in	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
can	O
build	O
the	O
third	ORDINAL
depot	O
afterwards	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
Zerg	PERSON
successfully	O
guesses	O
correctly	O
as	O
to	O
which	O
starting	O
position	O
you	O
are	O
at	O
,	O
then	O
his	O
Zerglings	O
will	O
arrive	O
while	O
your	O
Barracks	O
is	O
still	O
under	O
construction	O
.	O
You	O
will	O
have	O
to	O
pull	O
SCVs	O
to	O
your	O
ramp	O
or	O
choke	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
try	O
to	O
hold	O
off	O
his	O
Zerglings	O
until	O
you	O
can	O
get	O
a	O
Marine	O
out	O
to	O
defend	O
.	O
Proper	O
micro	O
is	O
key	O
to	O
defending	O
against	O
this	O
cheese	O
,	O
and	O
your	O
SCVs	O
should	O
always	O
be	O
acting	O
as	O
a	O
wall	O
between	O
the	O
Zerglings	O
and	O
your	O
Marine	O
.	O
Be	O
sure	O
to	O
retreat	O
the	O
Marine	O
if	O
necessary	O
,	O
though	O
the	O
best	O
play	O
would	O
be	O
to	O
try	O
to	O
circle	O
around	O
through	O
your	O
SCVs	O
so	O
the	O
chasing	O
Zerglings	PERSON
will	O
take	O
damage	O
from	O
your	O
SCVs	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
recommended	O
and	O
safe	O
for	O
players	O
to	O
double	O
scout	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
first	ORDINAL
SCV	O
sent	O
at	O
11	NUMBER
supply	O
reaches	O
the	O
natural	O
of	O
the	O
first	ORDINAL
scouted	O
location	O
-LRB-	O
you	O
have	O
confirmed	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
going	O
12	NUMBER
hatch	O
in	O
one	NUMBER
position	O
-RRB-	O
,	O
send	O
a	DURATION
second	DURATION
SCV	O
in	O
the	O
direction	O
opposite	O
of	O
the	O
first	ORDINAL
-LRB-	O
e.g.	O
.	O
If	O
your	O
first	ORDINAL
SCV	ORGANIZATION
scouted	O
clockwise	O
,	O
send	O
your	O
second	ORDINAL
SCV	O
counter-clockwise	O
-RRB-	O
.	O
If	O
timed	O
correctly	O
,	O
both	O
SCVs	O
will	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
scout	O
both	O
remaining	O
locations	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
Against	O
a	O
9	NUMBER
Pool	O
build	O
,	O
the	O
Zerg	PERSON
will	O
typically	O
try	O
to	O
scout	O
you	O
early	O
on	O
with	O
a	O
drone	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
early	O
lings	O
,	O
pull	O
4	NUMBER
to	O
5	NUMBER
SCVs	O
and	O
block	O
the	O
ramp/choke	O
point	O
and	O
plant	O
the	O
CC	O
in	O
your	O
main	O
and	O
float	O
it	O
over	O
later	O
.	O
Unless	O
the	O
Zerg	PERSON
went	O
9	NUMBER
pool	O
speed	O
,	O
you	O
can	O
usually	O
hide	O
one	NUMBER
of	O
your	O
initial	O
scouting	O
SCVs	O
and	O
scout	O
for	O
Zerg	PERSON
's	O
transition	O
-LRB-	O
1	NUMBER
base	O
tech	O
or	O
expansion	O
-RRB-	O
after	O
a	O
certain	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
transition	O
from	O
the	O
1	NUMBER
Rax	ORGANIZATION
FE	O
build	O
will	O
mostly	O
depend	O
on	O
whether	O
the	O
Zerg	PERSON
player	O
is	O
going	O
2	NUMBER
Hatch	PERSON
or	O
3	NUMBER
Hatch	PERSON
:	O
If	O
the	O
Zerg	PERSON
is	O
going	O
3	NUMBER
Hatch	PERSON
,	O
then	O
the	O
most	O
common	O
transition	O
is	O
to	O
set	O
up	O
for	O
the	DURATION
9	DURATION
Minute	DURATION
Push	O
.	O
For	O
a	O
far	O
more	O
aggressive	O
option	O
,	O
the	O
+1	NUMBER
5	NUMBER
Rax	ORGANIZATION
build	O
is	O
extremely	O
powerful	O
against	O
3	NUMBER
Hatch	PERSON
Mutas	PERSON
.	O
If	O
you	O
want	O
to	O
cheese	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
Ayumi	PERSON
Build	PERSON
is	O
viable	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
Zerg	PERSON
is	O
going	O
2	NUMBER
Hatch	PERSON
,	O
then	O
there	O
are	O
several	O
options	O
.	O
One	NUMBER
option	O
is	O
the	O
2	NUMBER
Rax	ORGANIZATION
Tech	ORGANIZATION
,	O
which	O
favors	O
a	O
passive	O
mid	O
game	O
in	O
favor	O
of	O
a	O
late	O
game	O
that	O
involves	O
more	O
Vessels	O
or	O
Tanks	O
.	O
The	O
more	O
common	O
transition	O
against	O
2	NUMBER
Hatch	PERSON
muta	O
is	O
to	O
add	O
a	O
3rd	ORGANIZATION
Barracks	ORGANIZATION
after	O
Ebay	ORGANIZATION
,	O
then	O
tech	O
up	O
to	O
Vessel	O
while	O
making	O
tanks	O
for	O
the	O
timing	O
attack	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
also	O
a	O
2	NUMBER
Barracks	ORGANIZATION
tech	O
variation	O
for	O
those	O
confident	O
in	O
their	O
m	O
&	O
m	O
control	O
that	O
gets	O
more	O
tanks	O
for	O
a	O
timing	O
attack	O
but	O
no	O
real	O
map	O
control	O
before	O
that	O
point	O
.	O
Lastly	O
,	O
one	NUMBER
can	O
open	O
4	NUMBER
Barracks	ORGANIZATION
before	O
Factory	O
to	O
put	O
a	O
large	O
amount	O
of	O
pressure	O
on	O
the	O
Zerg	PERSON
and	O
transition	O
into	O
SK	O
Terran	O
.	O
When	O
making	O
turrets	O
against	O
2	NUMBER
Hatch	PERSON
muta	O
,	O
only	O
one	NUMBER
scv	O
needs	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
turret	O
at	O
one	NUMBER
spot	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
Zerg	PERSON
's	O
first	ORDINAL
6	NUMBER
mutas	O
can	O
not	O
handle	O
a	O
turret	O
if	O
any	O
m	O
&	O
m	O
are	O
nearby	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
get	O
more	O
mutas	O
,	O
each	O
scv	O
will	O
have	O
completed	O
the	O
second	ORDINAL
and	O
potentially	O
3rd	ORDINAL
turret	O
.	O
The	O
exception	O
to	O
this	O
is	O
on	O
maps	O
like	O
Fighting	ORGANIZATION
Spirit	ORGANIZATION
where	O
the	O
Terran	MISC
must	O
make	O
a	O
large	O
number	O
of	O
turrets	O
at	O
a	O
specific	O
location	O
immediately	O
.	O
Flash	O
Vods	O
are	O
the	O
must-have	O
source	O
for	O
optimal	O
turret	O
placement	O
.	O
An	O
upgrade	O
rush	O
gets	O
+1	NUMBER
very	O
early	O
,	O
during	O
the	O
muta	O
harass	O
phase	O
,	O
and	O
gives	O
you	O
a	O
threatening	O
timing	O
window	O
before	O
lurkers	O
come	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
very	O
strong	O
midgame	O
army	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
however	O
much	O
weaker	O
against	O
ling	O
allins	O
and	O
thus	O
is	O
of	O
questionable	O
use	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
n't	O
somewhat	O
sure	O
of	O
their	O
opening	O
.	O
Note	O
that	O
this	O
works	O
against	O
both	O
2	NUMBER
hatch	O
and	O
3	NUMBER
hatch	O
muta	O
.	O
CC	ORGANIZATION
Refinery	ORGANIZATION
Ebay	ORGANIZATION
Academy	ORGANIZATION
Barracks	ORGANIZATION
2x	O
4th	ORDINAL
Barracks	O
or	O
Factory	O
.	O
Economic	O
2	NUMBER
Hatch	PERSON
Muta	PERSON
is	O
when	O
the	O
Zerg	PERSON
barely	O
builds	O
any	O
lings	O
and	O
takes	O
a	O
very	O
quick	O
3rd	ORDINAL
base	O
,	O
aiming	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
economy	O
while	O
harassing	O
.	O
Upgrade	O
rushes	O
are	O
very	O
potent	O
against	O
this	O
build	O
but	O
there	O
is	O
another	O
aggressive	O
strategy	O
that	O
can	O
pay	O
off	O
with	O
high	O
dividends	O
as	O
well	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
two	NUMBER
approaches	O
that	O
depend	O
on	O
the	O
map	O
in	O
question	O
.	O
On	O
maps	O
without	O
a	O
ramped	O
3rd	ORDINAL
or	O
just	O
one	NUMBER
that	O
is	O
more	O
difficult	O
to	O
defend	O
,	O
the	O
4	NUMBER
Rax	ORGANIZATION
variation	O
is	O
generally	O
better	O
and	O
is	O
also	O
more	O
forgiving	O
against	O
any	O
slipups	O
.	O
The	O
goal	O
of	O
this	O
strategy	O
is	O
to	O
save	O
money	O
on	O
turrets	O
and	O
depots	O
by	O
consistently	O
fighting	O
Mutas	O
in	O
the	O
open	O
field	O
.	O
The	O
Zerg	PERSON
must	O
make	O
lots	O
of	O
mutas	O
to	O
defend	O
with	O
because	O
they	O
ca	O
n't	O
defend	O
their	O
early	O
3rd	ORDINAL
and	O
natural	O
with	O
sunkens	O
and	O
thus	O
their	O
lurkers	O
and	O
general	O
timings	O
will	O
all	O
be	O
messed	O
up	O
.	O
It	O
requires	O
very	O
good	O
m	O
&	O
m	O
micro	O
but	O
is	O
definitely	O
one	NUMBER
of	O
the	O
best	O
contemporary	O
strategies	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
Zerg	PERSON
makes	O
any	O
mistakes	O
such	O
as	O
missing	O
the	O
marines	O
and	O
flying	O
straight	O
towards	O
your	O
base	O
or	O
not	O
making	O
a	O
sunken	O
you	O
can	O
kill	O
their	O
natural	O
and	O
just	O
win	O
.	O
Normal	O
games	O
will	O
involve	O
a	O
bunch	O
of	O
fighting	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
until	O
+1	NUMBER
and	O
sufficient	O
marine	O
count	O
makes	O
the	O
mutas	O
obsolete	O
.	O
But	O
always	O
be	O
careful	O
of	O
the	O
Zerg	PERSON
cutting	O
drones	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
lings	O
.	O
In	O
this	O
case	O
immediately	O
retreat	O
back	O
and	O
make	O
additional	O
turrets	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
get	O
3rd	ORDINAL
Rax	ORGANIZATION
before	O
Ebay	PERSON
then	O
you	O
will	O
need	O
to	O
delay	O
turrets	O
a	O
bit	O
and	O
ensure	O
that	O
you	O
catch	O
their	O
mutas	O
with	O
your	O
rines	O
or	O
make	O
sure	O
that	O
the	O
Zerg	PERSON
knows	O
the	O
threat	O
and	O
fights	O
your	O
marines	O
rather	O
than	O
runs	O
into	O
a	O
turretless	O
base	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
only	O
a	O
problem	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
targeting	O
their	O
3rd	ORDINAL
;	O
if	O
you	O
target	O
their	O
natural	O
and	O
they	O
go	O
for	O
your	O
main	O
the	O
Terran	MISC
ends	O
up	O
ahead	O
.	O
Standard	O
build	O
Add	O
2	NUMBER
Barracks	ORGANIZATION
after	O
Turrets	O
and	O
upgrades	O
started	O
.	O
Continually	O
press	O
out	O
with	O
new	O
m	O
&	O
m	O
groups	O
and	O
occupy	O
the	O
mutas	O
.	O
Factory	O
-LRB-	O
this	O
build	O
works	O
both	O
with	O
a	O
timing	O
attack	O
and	O
straight	O
up	O
SK	O
Terran	O
transition	O
-RRB-	O
Starport	O
-LRB-	O
make	O
dropship	O
asap	O
-RRB-	O
Science	O
Facility	O
and	O
2nd	DATE
Ebay	DATE
This	O
build	O
aims	O
to	O
put	O
constant	O
pressure	O
on	O
the	O
Zerg	ORGANIZATION
in	O
a	O
more	O
flowing	O
style	O
than	O
normal	O
.	O
The	O
4	NUMBER
Barracks	O
are	O
particularly	O
effective	O
at	O
pressuring	O
on	O
non-ramped	O
3rd	ORDINAL
maps	O
and	O
the	O
extra	O
marines	O
keep	O
the	O
Zerg	PERSON
preoccupied	O
while	O
they	O
are	O
being	O
set	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
drop	O
.	O
From	O
there	O
a	O
timing	O
attack	O
or	O
SK	O
Terran	O
is	O
possible	O
but	O
either	O
way	O
the	O
Zerg	PERSON
should	O
be	O
continually	O
threatened	O
and	O
thrown	O
off	O
their	O
gameplan	O
.	O
CC	ORGANIZATION
Barracks	ORGANIZATION
Refinery	ORGANIZATION
Academy	ORGANIZATION
Barracks	ORGANIZATION
Engineering	ORGANIZATION
Bay	ORGANIZATION
Turrets	ORGANIZATION
Factory	ORGANIZATION
Starport	O
Science	O
Facility	O
+	O
Engineering	O
Bay	O
While	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
mostly	O
discarded	O
in	O
favor	O
of	O
the	O
standard	O
approach	O
discussed	O
above	O
,	O
this	O
build	O
might	O
be	O
more	O
comforting	O
for	O
players	O
who	O
have	O
trouble	O
vs	O
ling	O
allins	O
as	O
it	O
gets	O
firebats	O
extremely	O
quickly	O
.	O
CC	ORGANIZATION
Refinery	ORGANIZATION
Academy	ORGANIZATION
Barracks	ORGANIZATION
x2	ORGANIZATION
Factory	ORGANIZATION
-LRB-	O
Commence	O
Tank	O
production	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
possible	O
and	O
siege	O
when	O
gas	O
allows	O
-RRB-	O
Engineering	LOCATION
Bay	LOCATION
Starport	LOCATION
Engineering	LOCATION
Bay	LOCATION
+	O
Science	O
Facility	O
This	O
type	O
of	O
play	O
has	O
been	O
popularized	O
mostly	O
by	O
Flash	O
in	O
this	O
match-up	O
.	O
The	O
basic	O
idea	O
is	O
getting	O
+1	NUMBER
weapons	O
when	O
mutalisks	O
arrive	O
whilst	O
teching	O
up	O
based	O
on	O
2	NUMBER
barracks	O
.	O
Since	O
this	O
build	O
has	O
a	O
low	O
barrack	O
count	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
perfectly	O
fine	O
to	O
be	O
adding	O
more	O
turrets	O
to	O
hold	O
off	O
mutalisks	O
along	O
with	O
your	O
first	ORDINAL
control	O
group	O
of	O
marines	O
and	O
medics	O
.	O
The	O
basics	O
of	O
this	O
build	O
follow	O
the	O
1	NUMBER
Rax	ORGANIZATION
FE	O
build	O
.	O
Here	O
are	O
the	O
details	O
:	O
2nd	ORDINAL
Rax	ORGANIZATION
added	O
at	O
approximately	O
22	NUMBER
supply	O
after	O
natural	O
command	O
center	O
is	O
building	O
.	O
Refinery	O
after	O
second	ORDINAL
Rax	ORGANIZATION
is	O
building	O
.	O
Ebay	ORGANIZATION
after	O
refinery	O
is	O
done	O
.	O
@	O
100	NUMBER
gas	O
,	O
remove	O
all	O
SCVs	O
from	O
gas	O
.	O
@	O
100	PERCENT
%	PERCENT
ebay	O
,	O
start	O
+1	NUMBER
weapons	O
@	O
100	PERCENT
%	PERCENT
ebay	O
,	O
start	O
academy	O
,	O
3	NUMBER
SCVs	O
back	O
on	O
gas	O
.	O
+1	NUMBER
weapons	O
should	O
complete	O
when	O
mutalisks	O
arrive	O
and	O
the	O
+1	NUMBER
weapons	O
should	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
huge	O
lead	O
in	O
defending	O
against	O
his	O
flock	O
.	O
+1	NUMBER
armour	O
is	O
usually	O
followed	O
after	O
+1	NUMBER
attack	O
.	O
Factory	O
should	O
be	O
started	O
once	DATE
your	O
stim	O
is	O
being	O
researched	O
.	O
3rd	ORDINAL
and	ORDINAL
4th	ORDINAL
rax	O
added	O
after	O
you	O
plant	O
down	O
your	O
starport	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
also	O
important	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
proper	O
medic	O
to	O
marine	O
ratio	O
.	O
Since	O
you	O
are	O
staying	O
on	O
2	NUMBER
rax	O
for	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
important	O
to	O
also	O
protect	O
your	O
medics	O
and	O
to	O
make	O
at	O
least	O
2	NUMBER
more	O
after	O
your	O
initial	O
group	O
of	O
marines	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
get	O
the	O
timings	O
correct	O
,	O
+2	NUMBER
weapons	O
can	O
be	O
researched	O
right	O
after	O
+1	NUMBER
armour	O
is	O
done	O
.	O
This	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
very	O
strong	O
mid-game	O
pre-defiler	O
army	O
consisting	O
of	O
around	O
2	NUMBER
control	O
groups	O
of	O
marines	O
,	O
2	NUMBER
tanks	O
and	O
a	O
vessel	O
.	O
This	O
approach	O
can	O
significantly	O
delay	O
the	O
Zerg	ORGANIZATION
's	O
3rd	ORDINAL
gas	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
generally	O
enough	O
to	O
win	O
the	O
game	O
with	O
a	O
followup	O
timing	O
attack	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
usable	O
so	O
long	O
as	O
the	O
Zerg	PERSON
is	O
not	O
going	O
allin	O
,	O
but	O
unlike	O
the	O
aggressive	O
approach	O
vs	O
2	NUMBER
hatch	O
muta	O
this	O
build	O
can	O
handle	O
medium	O
amounts	O
of	O
Zerglings	O
.	O
Unlike	O
in	O
the	O
2	NUMBER
hatch	O
version	O
turrets	O
do	O
not	O
need	O
to	O
be	O
delayed	O
.	O
The	O
goal	O
here	O
is	O
to	O
delay	O
the	O
Zerg	PERSON
's	O
3rd	ORDINAL
gas	O
long	O
enough	O
so	O
that	O
they	O
do	O
n't	O
have	O
the	O
gas	O
to	O
defend	O
against	O
the	O
pre-defiler	O
timing	O
attack	O
.	O
The	O
threat	O
of	O
a	O
counterattack	O
is	O
not	O
as	O
big	O
here	O
so	O
long	O
as	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
bunker	O
at	O
the	O
natural	O
with	O
a	O
firebat	O
inside	O
,	O
instead	O
,	O
the	O
main	O
difficulty	O
is	O
ensuring	O
muta/ling	O
does	O
not	O
pick	O
off	O
isolated	O
groups	O
of	O
infantry	O
or	O
that	O
the	O
base	O
is	O
completely	O
undefended	O
when	O
a	O
counter	O
comes	O
.	O
CC	ORGANIZATION
Barracks	ORGANIZATION
Refinery	ORGANIZATION
Academy	ORGANIZATION
Barracks	ORGANIZATION
Engineering	ORGANIZATION
Bay	ORGANIZATION
Factory	ORGANIZATION
12	NUMBER
pool	O
Lair	O
is	O
an	O
aggressive	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
necessarily	O
allin	O
Mutalisk	O
build	O
.	O
The	O
standard	O
build	O
must	O
be	O
adapted	O
slightly	O
with	O
an	O
earlier	O
Engineering	O
bay	O
and	O
turrets	O
.	O
More	O
turrets	O
should	O
be	O
built	O
than	O
normal	O
because	O
the	O
Zerg	PERSON
absolutely	O
must	O
do	O
damage	O
with	O
their	O
Mutas	O
or	O
they	O
will	O
be	O
rather	O
behind	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
Terran	MISC
player	O
has	O
confidence	O
in	O
their	O
micro	O
vs	O
mutalisks	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
strong	O
strategy	O
against	O
a	O
low	O
ling	O
count	O
approach	O
.	O
3rd	ORDINAL
Barracks	O
after	O
Turrets	O
Tech	O
to	O
Science	O
Vessels	O
and	O
Irradiate	O
ASAP	O
.	O
Produce	O
tanks	O
when	O
possible	O
but	O
do	O
n't	O
delay	O
Vessels	O
.	O
Once	DATE
enough	O
turrets	O
are	O
made	O
to	O
defend	O
immediately	O
start	O
threatening	O
to	O
attack	O
the	O
Zerg	PERSON
's	O
natural	O
.	O
The	O
Zerg	PERSON
will	O
have	O
to	O
defend	O
with	O
mutas	O
and	O
will	O
likely	O
kill	O
off	O
a	O
few	O
groups	O
.	O
The	O
critical	O
timing	O
to	O
pressure	O
either	O
their	O
3rd	ORDINAL
or	O
natural	O
is	O
when	O
they	O
cut	O
muta	O
production	O
to	O
make	O
lurkers	O
.	O
The	O
Vessel	O
comes	O
out	O
around	O
this	O
time	O
as	O
well	O
so	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
much	O
easier	O
to	O
fight	O
versus	O
mutas	O
and	O
you	O
will	O
likely	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
force	O
sunkens	O
or	O
cause	O
some	O
kind	O
of	O
damage	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
time	O
this	O
attack	O
is	O
done	O
with	O
a	O
followup	O
army	O
with	O
Tanks	O
and	O
a	O
Vessel	O
should	O
win	O
the	O
game	O
handily	O
.	O
Because	O
12	NUMBER
Pool	O
Lair	O
is	O
a	O
weaker	O
build	O
economically	O
the	O
Zerg	PERSON
does	O
not	O
have	O
the	O
drone	O
count	O
to	O
make	O
any	O
number	O
of	O
sunkens	O
,	O
they	O
must	O
defend	O
with	O
mutas	O
long	O
enough	O
until	O
lurkers	O
come	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
concept	O
behind	O
this	O
strategy	O
is	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Zerg	PERSON
fight	O
uneconomical	O
battles	O
by	O
continually	O
attacking	O
them	O
with	O
sufficient	O
numbers	O
of	O
m	O
&	O
m	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
Zerg	PERSON
ignores	O
the	O
m	O
&	O
m	O
they	O
will	O
have	O
to	O
kill	O
their	O
economy	O
to	O
sunken	O
enough	O
and	O
abandon	O
any	O
hope	O
of	O
a	O
3rd	ORDINAL
base	O
and	O
any	O
mutalisk	O
counter	O
should	O
be	O
adequately	O
delayed	O
by	O
the	O
extra	O
turrets	O
made	O
until	O
the	O
marines	O
make	O
it	O
home	O
.	O
Thus	O
the	O
Zerg	PERSON
must	O
fight	O
the	O
m	O
&	O
m	O
with	O
almost	O
pure	O
mutas	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
Zerg	PERSON
has	O
normal	O
drone	O
count	O
and	O
is	O
going	O
lurkers	O
instead	O
of	O
mutas	O
or	O
has	O
a	O
spire	O
and	O
den	O
and	O
is	O
not	O
saving	O
larvae	O
you	O
can	O
be	O
much	O
more	O
aggressive	O
and	O
contain	O
them	O
immediately	O
.	O
If	O
they	O
make	O
too	O
few	O
lings	O
early	O
then	O
you	O
can	O
pretty	O
much	O
camp	O
in	O
front	O
of	O
their	O
natural	O
and	O
delay	O
any	O
expansion	O
attempts	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
a	O
lot	O
more	O
freedom	O
against	O
lurker	O
first	ORDINAL
openings	O
but	O
a	O
timing	O
push	O
is	O
a	O
must	O
either	O
way	O
.	O
Scouting	O
ling	O
allins	O
is	O
an	O
absolute	O
must	O
.	O
Hide	O
an	O
scv	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
before	O
his	O
lings	O
arrive	O
at	O
your	O
natural	O
.	O
Use	O
it	O
after	O
your	O
first	ORDINAL
one	NUMBER
dies	O
and	O
his	O
lings	O
have	O
left	O
his	O
base	O
to	O
scout	O
his	O
drone	O
count	O
,	O
sunken	O
count	O
,	O
and	O
tech	O
choice	O
.	O
Alternatively	O
you	O
can	O
just	O
have	O
it	O
camp	O
in	O
front	O
of	O
his	O
natural	O
to	O
know	O
when	O
he	O
will	O
expand	O
and	O
if	O
any	O
lings	O
are	O
leaving	O
his	O
base	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
see	O
few	O
drones	O
and/or	O
many	O
lings	O
make	O
a	O
bunker	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
have	O
one	NUMBER
already	O
,	O
depot	O
in	O
front	O
of	O
the	O
bunker	O
at	O
an	O
angle	O
that	O
blocks	O
lings/lets	O
scvs	O
repair	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
hotkey	O
your	O
nat	O
scvs	O
and	O
an	O
area	O
hotkey	O
in	O
your	O
main	O
mineral	O
line	O
.	O
Keep	O
your	O
rallied	O
marines	O
on	O
the	O
ramp	O
and	O
have	O
an	O
scv	O
about	O
a	O
screen	O
away	O
from	O
your	O
nat	O
to	O
give	O
advance	O
warning	O
of	O
allin	O
.	O
If	O
he	O
goes	O
in	O
have	O
the	O
scvs	O
immediately	O
run	O
towards	O
the	O
bunker	O
and	O
bring	O
the	O
rallied	O
marines	O
forward	O
.	O
If	O
he	O
tries	O
to	O
run	O
into	O
the	O
main	O
send	O
your	O
scvs	O
to	O
mine	O
at	O
the	O
main	O
and	O
have	O
them	O
stop	O
in	O
front	O
of	O
the	O
rallied	O
marines	O
at	O
the	O
ramp	O
and	O
attack	O
.	O
After	O
you	O
block	O
it	O
immediately	O
prepare	O
for	O
his	O
tech	O
choice	O
-LRB-	O
generally	O
mutas	O
-RRB-	O
.	O
Once	DATE
you	O
defend	O
against	O
that	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
pretty	O
easy	O
to	O
win	O
with	O
a	O
simple	O
pre-defiler	O
timing	O
attack	O
.	O
Every	O
variant	O
of	O
1	NUMBER
Rax	O
FE	O
is	O
geared	O
towards	O
maximizing	O
its	O
strengths	O
against	O
one	NUMBER
or	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
following	O
timing	O
windows	O
while	O
still	O
remaining	O
flexible	O
enough	O
to	O
adapt	O
to	O
any	O
circumstance	O
.	O
The	O
changes	O
in	O
build	O
order	O
may	O
be	O
slight	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
important	O
to	O
optimize	O
your	O
build	O
for	O
a	O
specific	O
plan	O
that	O
exploits	O
one	NUMBER
or	O
more	O
timing	O
windows	O
.	O
Post-Muta	O
timing	O
windows	O
heavily	O
depend	O
on	O
how	O
and	O
how	O
well	O
you	O
handled	O
the	O
muta	O
harass	O
.	O
If	O
mutas	O
do	O
a	O
lot	O
of	O
damage	O
it	O
is	O
difficult	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
damage	O
here	O
but	O
if	O
they	O
are	O
brushed	O
aside	O
the	O
Zerg	PERSON
is	O
in	O
immediate	O
danger	O
.	O
Sometimes	O
the	O
Zerg	PERSON
might	O
gamble	O
that	O
they	O
will	O
do	O
enough	O
damage	O
with	O
mutalisks	O
and	O
therefore	O
delay	O
lurkers	O
.	O
In	O
those	O
situations	O
if	O
the	O
Mutas	O
do	O
little	O
damage	O
the	O
game	O
can	O
generally	O
be	O
ended	O
by	O
simply	O
breaking	O
their	O
natural	O
before	O
lurkers	O
are	O
done	O
.	O
Another	O
easy	O
mistake	O
to	O
catch	O
Zergs	O
on	O
is	O
if	O
they	O
are	O
slow	O
on	O
getting	O
hydras	O
to	O
their	O
3rd	ORDINAL
if	O
they	O
did	O
3	NUMBER
hatch	O
mutalisk	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
often	O
too	O
late	O
if	O
they	O
simply	O
morph	O
lurkers	O
at	O
their	O
natural	O
then	O
run	O
them	O
over	O
to	O
defend	O
the	O
3rd	ORDINAL
.	O
In	O
general	O
the	O
goal	O
of	O
this	O
timing	O
window	O
is	O
to	O
micro	O
against	O
mutas	O
in	O
the	O
open	O
field	O
and	O
thus	O
force	O
sunkens	O
and	O
delay	O
their	O
3rd	ORDINAL
base	O
for	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
possible	O
.	O
The	O
most	O
important	O
criteria	O
here	O
is	O
to	O
judge	O
how	O
safe	O
your	O
base	O
is	O
to	O
a	O
counterattack	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
safely	O
venture	O
out	O
versus	O
muta/ling	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
Zerg	PERSON
makes	O
a	O
lot	O
of	O
Zerglings	O
it	O
is	O
better	O
to	O
simply	O
defend	O
versus	O
Mutas	O
and	O
attack	O
in	O
the	O
pre-defiler	O
window	O
because	O
they	O
will	O
be	O
weaker	O
economically	O
.	O
Therefore	O
pressuring	O
in	O
this	O
timing	O
window	O
is	O
generally	O
limited	O
to	O
more	O
economical	O
Zerg	PERSON
strategies	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
venture	O
out	O
to	O
kill/threaten	O
their	O
3rd	ORDINAL
,	O
and	O
the	O
Zerg	PERSON
counterattacks	O
,	O
the	O
best	O
approach	O
is	O
to	O
split	O
off	O
a	O
group	O
of	O
6	NUMBER
or	O
so	O
marines	O
and	O
a	O
medic	O
to	O
stim	O
and	O
kill	O
their	O
3rd	ORDINAL
while	O
the	O
rest	O
goes	O
home	O
to	O
defend	O
.	O
Builds	O
that	O
jump	O
to	O
SK	O
Terran	O
directly	O
are	O
the	O
most	O
optimized	O
against	O
this	O
particular	O
timing	O
window	O
but	O
pre-defiler	O
timing	O
attacks	O
will	O
transition	O
into	O
SK	O
Terran	O
nicely	O
enough	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
two	NUMBER
goals	O
here	O
,	O
namely	O
to	O
prevent	O
the	O
Zerg	PERSON
from	O
taking	O
their	O
4th	ORDINAL
base	O
and	O
to	O
secure	O
a	O
3rd	ORDINAL
base	O
.	O
Both	O
are	O
accomplished	O
by	O
maintaining	O
a	O
constant	O
amount	O
of	O
pressure	O
on	O
the	O
Zerg	PERSON
and	O
forcing	O
them	O
to	O
barely	O
defend	O
everywhere	O
at	O
once	DATE
.	O
On	O
maps	O
with	O
difficult	O
terrain	O
as	O
Outsider	O
or	O
Ultimatum	O
where	O
additional	O
expansions	O
are	O
not	O
kept	O
on	O
land	O
it	O
is	O
worth	O
it	O
to	O
put	O
a	O
small	O
group	O
of	O
infantry	O
to	O
delay	O
any	O
future	DATE
Zerg	PERSON
expansions	O
.	O
While	O
SK	O
Terran	O
demands	O
a	O
constant	O
stream	O
of	O
Vessels	O
it	O
's	O
recommended	O
for	O
the	O
aggressive	O
minded	O
player	O
to	O
substitute	O
in	O
dropships	O
at	O
times	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
pressure	O
on	O
.	O
A	O
particularly	O
nice	O
timing	O
window	O
for	O
a	O
combined	O
two	NUMBER
dropship	O
drop	O
plus	O
the	O
main	O
army	O
attacking	O
another	O
location	O
first	ORDINAL
is	O
right	O
when	O
the	O
Zerg	PERSON
secures	O
their	O
4th	ORDINAL
and	O
is	O
transitioning	O
into	O
Ultralisks	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
Defiler	O
and	O
Ultra	O
production	O
facilities	O
go	O
down	O
there	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
gaping	O
hole	O
in	O
the	O
Zerg	PERSON
's	O
defense	O
that	O
can	O
be	O
easily	O
exploited	O
.	O
This	O
attack	O
can	O
be	O
particularly	O
devastating	O
since	O
the	O
Zerg	PERSON
is	O
generally	O
stretched	O
out	O
trying	O
to	O
defend	O
3-4	NUMBER
bases	O
with	O
lurker/ling/swarm	O
.	O
Most	O
Zergs	O
will	O
generally	O
try	O
to	O
just	O
defend	O
until	O
they	O
can	O
get	O
4	NUMBER
gas	O
and	O
Ultralisks	O
going	O
but	O
some	O
will	O
go	O
for	O
a	O
more	O
aggressive	O
approach	O
once	DATE
consume	O
is	O
done	O
.	O
Against	O
the	O
former	O
it	O
is	O
better	O
to	O
spread	O
out	O
the	O
army	O
to	O
pressure	O
multiple	O
spots	O
and	O
do	O
larger	O
drops	O
at	O
once	DATE
.	O
Versus	O
the	O
latter	O
,	O
keeping	O
the	O
army	O
together	O
and	O
doing	O
smaller	O
drops	O
will	O
work	O
better	O
.	O
In	O
either	O
case	O
the	O
Terran	MISC
army	O
should	O
always	O
be	O
near	O
a	O
Zerg	LOCATION
base	O
or	O
at	O
least	O
controlling	O
the	O
middle	O
until	O
upgraded	O
Ultralisks	O
are	O
out	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
group	O
of	O
lurker/ling	O
under	O
swarm	O
can	O
completely	O
shut	O
down	O
a	O
Terran	MISC
base	O
if	O
they	O
reach	O
it	O
unopposed	O
.	O
On	O
maps	O
that	O
support	O
the	O
expansion	O
count	O
such	O
as	O
Outsider	O
and	O
most	O
4	NUMBER
player	O
maps	O
the	O
Terran	MISC
should	O
transition	O
to	O
a	O
more	O
tank	O
based	O
army	O
after	O
taking	O
a	O
4th	ORDINAL
base	O
.	O
Vessels	O
should	O
still	O
be	O
produced	O
out	O
of	O
2	NUMBER
ports	O
but	O
the	O
remaining	O
gas	O
should	O
be	O
used	O
to	O
make	O
tanks	O
at	O
both	O
mains	O
.	O
This	O
helps	O
prevent	O
very	O
dangerous	O
lategame	O
counterattacks	O
.	O
The	O
most	O
important	O
part	O
of	O
lategame	O
play	O
is	O
to	O
ensure	O
that	O
every	O
defiler	O
gets	O
irradiated	O
and	O
that	O
their	O
ultralisks	O
get	O
worn	O
down	O
before	O
any	O
battles	O
start	O
.	O
Sometimes	O
Vessels	O
will	O
have	O
to	O
be	O
suicided	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
do	O
this	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
absolutely	O
necessary	O
to	O
hurt	O
the	O
Zerg	LOCATION
army	O
before	O
it	O
is	O
engaged	O
.	O
Only	O
after	O
the	O
Zerg	PERSON
has	O
been	O
weakened	O
by	O
irradiates	O
and	O
all	O
defilers	O
are	O
dead	O
should	O
the	O
Terran	O
try	O
to	O
fight	O
it	O
without	O
tank	O
support	O
.	O
In	O
general	O
tanks	O
should	O
be	O
set	O
up	O
at	O
both	O
mains	O
and	O
the	O
m	O
&	O
m	O
force	O
roam	O
around	O
to	O
cover	O
Vessels	O
Once	DATE
a	O
sufficient	O
mass	O
of	O
tanks	O
has	O
been	O
built	O
up	O
the	O
Terran	O
can	O
try	O
to	O
end	O
the	O
game	O
in	O
one	NUMBER
attack	O
or	O
map	O
depending	O
,	O
just	O
defend	O
and	O
deny	O
the	O
Zerg	PERSON
any	O
more	O
bases	O
.	O
If	O
a	O
mass	O
tank	O
attack	O
is	O
made	O
the	O
most	O
important	O
goal	O
again	O
is	O
to	O
make	O
sure	O
no	O
defiler	O
enters	O
the	O
battle	O
.	O
If	O
every	O
Vessel	O
is	O
suicided	O
for	O
that	O
goal	O
it	O
is	O
okay	O
because	O
Zerg	PERSON
can	O
not	O
hope	O
to	O
beat	O
a	O
mass	O
of	O
tanks	O
backed	O
by	O
a	O
significant	O
number	O
of	O
infantry	O
without	O
dark	O
swarm	O
and	O
plague	O
and	O
that	O
attack	O
is	O
generally	O
the	O
game	O
ender	O
.	O
http://www.teamliquid.net/tlpd/games/34970_Calm_vs_Flash/vod	O
-LRB-	O
EotS	O
,	O
aggressive	O
3	NUMBER
rax	O
tech	O
vs	O
econ	O
2	NUMBER
hatch	O
-RRB-	O
http://www.teamliquid.net/tlpd/games/34969_Calm_vs_Flash/vod	O
-LRB-	O
FS	O
,	O
lategame	O
tank	O
play	O
-RRB-	O
http://www.teamliquid.net/tlpd/games/34967_Calm_vs_Flash/vod	O
-LRB-	O
El	ORGANIZATION
Nino	ORGANIZATION
,	O
12	NUMBER
pool	O
lair	O
-RRB-	O
http://www.teamliquid.net/tlpd/games/31182_Flash_vs_HoGiL	O
-LRB-	O
El	LOCATION
Nino	LOCATION
,	O
Standard	O
Timing	O
Attack	O
-RRB-	O
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HElWCJDELV8	O
-LRB-	O
Flash/Zero	O
,	O
Ultimatum	O
,	O
lategame	O
decision	O
making	O
guide	O
-RRB-	O
http://www.teamliquid.net/tlpd/games/30613_Flash_vs_HyuN	O
-LRB-	O
Tornado	O
,	O
abnormal	O
timing	O
attack	O
-RRB-	O
http://www.teamliquid.net/tlpd/games/30573_Flash_vs_Kwanro	O
-LRB-	O
FS	O
,	O
muta	O
defense	O
+	O
timing	O
attack	O
from	O
2	NUMBER
rax	O
tech	O
-RRB-	O
http://www.teamliquid.net/tlpd/games/34843_Flash_vs_Jaedong	O
-LRB-	O
FS	O
,	O
delaying	O
3rd	ORDINAL
vs	O
3	NUMBER
hatch	O
muta	O
-RRB-	O
http://www.teamliquid.net/tlpd/games/11301_Flash_vs_hyvaa	O
-LRB-	O
RH3	O
,	O
2	NUMBER
hatch	O
muta	O
into	O
3	NUMBER
gas	O
guards	O
-RRB-	O
http://www.teamliquid.net/tlpd/games/11189_Flash_vs_Jaedong	O
-LRB-	O
SCR	O
,	O
SK	O
Terran	O
vs	O
2	NUMBER
hatch	O
muta	O
-RRB-	O
http://www.teamliquid.net/tlpd/games/11155_Flash_vs_Jaedong	O
-LRB-	O
Harmony	O
,	O
2	NUMBER
hatch	O
muta	O
lurker	O
into	O
guards	O
-RRB-	O
http://www.teamliquid.net/tlpd/games/30600_Flash_vs_hero	O
-LRB-	O
HBR	O
,	O
Aggressive	O
4	NUMBER
rax	O
vs	O
economic	O
2	NUMBER
hatch	O
muta	O
-RRB-	O
http://www.teamliquid.net/tlpd/games/25090_fantasy_vs_Jaedong	O
-LRB-	O
Outsider	O
,	O
lategame	O
play	O
with	O
tank	O
timing	O
-RRB-	O
http://www.teamliquid.net/tlpd/games/34773_Flash_vs_type-b	O
-LRB-	O
EotS	O
,	O
2	NUMBER
base	O
8	NUMBER
rax	O
allin	O
vs	O
muta	O
-	O
>	O
ultra	O
-RRB-	O
http://www.teamliquid.net/tlpd/games/10605_Flash_vs_GGPlay	O
-LRB-	O
Athena	ORGANIZATION
,	O
timing	O
vs	O
4	NUMBER
gas	O
hive	O
-RRB-	O
http://www.teamliquid.net/tlpd/games/9927_Flash_vs_July	O
-LRB-	O
RotK	O
,	O
3	NUMBER
gas	O
muta	O
allin	O
-RRB-	O
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0ZNeRktDWhA	O
-LRB-	O
Flash/Zero	O
,	O
Odd-Eye	PERSON
,	O
12	NUMBER
pool	O
lair	O
into	O
3	NUMBER
gas	O
guardian	O
-RRB-	O
http://www.teamliquid.net/tlpd/games/9311_Flash_vs_YellOw[ArnC]	O
-LRB-	O
Col	O
1	NUMBER
,	O
semi-allin	O
mutaling	O
-RRB-	O
http://www.teamliquid.net/tlpd/games/11452_Flash_vs_YellOw[ArnC]	O
-LRB-	O
Andro	O
,	O
allin	O
muta	O
-RRB-	O
http://www.teamliquid.net/forum/viewmessage.php?topic_id=78677	O
